Finding Aid to The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Photographs MS.57
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Joseph Hirshhorn, Early 1970s; 2006.6.916; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "22980-3"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Olga and Joseph Hirshhorn, Early 1970s; 2006.6.917; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." (repeated 2x) Handwritten on verso: "22980-33"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Olga and Joseph Hirshhorn, Early 1970s; 2006.6.918; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso; Stamp of Doris Bry on versoStamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF", "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N. Y." Handwritten on verso: "22980-11"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Hitching a Ride to Abiquiu with Maurice Grosser, 1944; 2006.6.923; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001; 1 Photographic Prints proof print 9 3/4 x 6 1/4 inches; Handwritten on verso: Proof copy 'Georgia O'Keeffe hitching a ride to Abiquiu with Maurice Grosser' Not part of titleHandwritten on verso: "CHABOT 1" "Proof Print original 5 3/4" x 9 5/8" be blown up to 8" x roughly 12"" "Maria Chabot 1992 'G O'K Georgia O'Keeffe Hitching a Ride to Abiquiu with Maurice Grosser'" "1945." scratched out "1944" "not part of title" "Bulller Hu 13 5" ? "20" circled Printed on verso: "Agfa"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Standing by Salita Door, 1960; 2006.6.924; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 15/16 x 7 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum Label on versoLabel on verso: Amon Carter Museum 'Title: Georgia O'Keeffe, Artist: Laura Gilpin, 1960'; stamp on verso: For study purposes only
- Georgia O'Keeffe Standing by Salita Door, 1960; 2006.6.925; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 10 1/8 x 7 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum Label on versoStamp on recto: "PRINTED BY THE AMON CARTER MUSEUM" Printed on recto: "KODAK- S AFETY- FILM 22" vertical and reversed Handwritten on verso: "GILPIN 42" Label on verso: "AMON CARTER MUSEUM Post Office Box 2365 3501 Camp Bowie Boulevard Fort Worth, Texas 76113 Museum Number LJ 5019 [18] 1960 Title ARCHITECTURE: O'KEEFFE RESIDENCE Artist Laura Gilpin Size Medium Date Date of Negative This picture may be reproduced only with written permission from the Amon Carter Museum and must be accompanied by the credit line: Courtesy Amon Carter Museum, Fort Worth, Texas." Stamp on verso: "NOTICE: This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner and must be accompanied by the credit line: Amon Carter Museum Courtesy Laura Gilpin Collection
- Georgia O'Keeffe Standing by Salita Door, 1960; 2006.6.926; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 15/16 x 7 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum Label on versoLabel on verso: Amon Carter Museum 'Title: Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence, Artist: Laura Gilpin, 1960'; Stamp on verso: For study purposes only
- Georgia O'Keeffe Standing by Salita Door, 1960; 2006.6.927; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 10 1/16 x 7 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum Label on versoStamp on recto: "PRINTED BY THE AMON CARTER MUSEUM" Printed on recto: "KODAK- S AFETY- FILM 22" vertical and reversed Handwritten on verso: "GILPIN 28" Label on verso: "AMON CARTER MUSEUM Post Office Box 2365 3501 Camp Bowie Boulevard Fort Worth, Texas 76113 Museum Number LJ 5019 [1] 1960 Title ARCHITECTURE: O'KEEFFE RESIDENCE Artist Laura Gilpin Size Medium Date Date of Negative This picture may be reproduced only with written permission from the Amon Carter Museum and must be accompanied by the credit line: Courtesy Amon Carter Museum, Fort Worth, Texas." Stamp on verso: "NOTICE: This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner and must be accompanied by the credit line: Amon Carter Museum Courtesy Laura Gilpin Collection
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Bedroom, 1960; 2006.6.928; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 10 x 8 1/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum Label on versoStamp on recto: "PRINTED BY THE AMON CARTER MUSEUM" Handwritten on verso: "GILPIN 27" Label on verso: "AMON CARTER MUSEUM Post Office Box 2365 3501 Camp Bowie Boulevard Fort Worth, Texas 76113 Museum Number LJ 4407 [26] May-June, 1960 Title ARCHITECTURE: O'KEEFFE RESIDENCE Artist Laura Gilpin Size Medium Date Date of Negative This picture may be reproduced only with written permission from the Amon Carter Museum and must be accompanied by the credit line: Courtesy Amon Carter Museum, Fort Worth, Texas." Stamp on verso: "NOTICE: This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner and must be accompanied by the credit line: Amon Carter Museum Courtesy Laura Gilpin Collection
  Portrait of O'Keeffe dressed in a robe, with an outstretched arm, placing rocks along a ledge in her bedroom; silver Navajo necklace hanging on wall, Japanese paper lamp shade suspended from ceiling, and light bulb clipped to the headboard of O'Keeffe's bed.
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1956; 2006.6.929; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 10 x 8 1/8 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the inscription: Karsh 1 18, and a lengthy label from the Spencer Museum of Art describing rights and reproduction usage and tombstone information.
  Striking profile portrait of O'Keeffe dressed in black, seated on the banco at the entrance of her Abiquiu house under a large set of elk antlers, exquisite tonal range, white shafts of ambient light falling on her forehead through the doorway.
  Copyright Estate of Yousuf Karsh
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Studio, 1965; 2006.6.930; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; Stamp of Balthazar Korab on versoStamp on verso: "BALTAZAR KORAB Above credit line necessary on publication. Ref. No. Baltazar Korab, 950 N. Hunter Birmingham, MICH. Midwest 6-9889" "H624" Handwritten on verso: "KORAB 1" "ArizonA NASHER"
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Living Room, 1965; 2006.6.931; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 7 1/2 x 9 3/8 inches; Stamp of Balthazar Korab on versoStamp on verso: "THIS PRINT IS SOLD FOR REFERENCE ONLY. NOT BE RESOLD, LOANED, REPRODUCED OR SYNDICATED WITHOUT SPECIAL WRITTEN PERMISSION OF THE PHOTOGRAPHER. REF # BALTAZAR KORAB 9509. HUNTER BLVD. BIRMINGHAM, MICHIGAN MI. 6-9889"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1930; 2006.6.932; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 3/4 x 7 13/16 inches; Printed on recto: "10" Handwritten on verso: "Return to O'Keeffe"
  Portrait of Georgia O'Keeffe standing in front of her painting, 'After a Walk Back of Mabel's', 1929 (CR0680). The photograph was probably made during O'Keeffe's 1930 exhibition at An American Place. copy print photography by Peter A. Juley and Sons.
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1930; 2006.6.933; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 5/8 x 7 1/2 inches; Peter A. Juley and Sons stamp on versoHandwritten on verso: "Return to O'Keeffe" "40." Stamp on verso: "Peter A. Juley & Son Photographers of Fine Art SINCE 1896 ?19 East 39th Street- New York City"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1930; 2006.6.934; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 13/16 x 7 15/16 inches; Printed on recto: "10"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1930; 2006.6.935; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 13/16 x 10 7/8 inches; Printed on recto: "10"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1930; 2006.6.936; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 13/16 x 7 7/8 inches; Note on verso: Peter Juley from Env. 'Large Photos'Printed on recto: "10" Handwritten on verso: "R. O'Keeffe" Label on verso: "52" Post-it on verso: "Peter Juley from env. (Large Photos)"
- Gardening, Abiquiu, 1966; 2006.6.937; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 12 5/16 x 8 3/16 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the inscription: OK, a Loengard studio and a lengthy stamp describing publication usage.
  Profile portrait of O'Keeffe working in her garden wearing a large flowered quilted jacket and a head scarf, surrounded by leaves and foliage.
- Walk, Ghost Ranch, 1967; 2006.6.938; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 8 1/16 x 12 1/4 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is a negative number, a Loengard studio stamp, and a lengthy stamp describing publication usage.
  Profile portrait of O'Keeffe walking her dogs on the Ghost Ranch property through native grasses and trees surrounded by hills. O'Keeffe wears a large flowered quilted jacket and a dark skirt and carries a staff-like walking stick.
- Ghost Ranch, 1967; 2006.6.939; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 8 1/16 x 12 1/16 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is a negative number, a Loengard studio stamp, and a lengthy stamp describing publication usage.
  Portrait of O'Keeffe in the courtyard of her Ghost Ranch house bending down to write on a wooden shipping crate (possibly for a painting). She is wearing a black wrap dress, a crocheted shawl and sheepkined lined suede booties. Bones and antlers visible on shelf in background.
- Georgia O'Keeffe, 1979; 2006.6.942; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: 79-48-3Handwritten on verso: '79-48-3'
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Juan Hamilton in Abiquiu Studio, 1979; 2006.6.943; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: 78-48-1Handwritten on verso: '78-48-1 mang 32'
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Studio, 1979; 2006.6.944; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp with Fred Mang and US Dept. of Interior on verso; Handwritten on verso: 79-49-11Stamp on verso: 'US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang Jr.'; stamp on verso: Kodak Feb 79; Handwritten on verso: '79-49-11 mang 44'
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Studio, 1979; 2006.6.945; Mang, Fred E., Jr., b. 1923; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; Stamp with Fred Mang and US Dept. of Interior on verso; Handwritten on verso: 1/23/79Handwritten on verso: "MANG 52" "1/23/79" Stamp on verso: "US Department of Interior National Park Service Photo By Fred Mang, Jr."
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Alfred Stieglitz at Lake George, 1932; 2006.6.946; Marks, Josephine B.; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 10 1/4 x 8 inches; Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library Yale University; Handwritten on verso: Newman, Arnold Photo of Georgia O'Keeffe and Alfred Stieglitz, n.d.Handwritten on verso: "Za St 34 + G2 2:2:G" "Newman, Arnold Photo of Georgia O'Keeffe and Alfred Stieglitz, n.d." Stamp on verso: "BEINECKE RARE BOOK AND MANUSCRIPT LIBRARY YALE UNIVERSITY" FOR REFERENCE USE ONLY Reproduced from the original The Yale University Library Permission necessary for reproduction or republication." "NOTICE: This material may be protected by copyright law (Title 17 U.S. Code)"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Press Club Award, 1946; 2006.6.947; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 8 1/8 x 9 7/8 inches; Jackie Martin Stamp on versoStamp on verso: "Photographs by Jackie Martin"
- Georgia O'Keeffe on Camelback in Morocco, 1974; 2006.6.948; Hamilton, Juan, b. 1945; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 15/16 x 8 inches; Stamp of Robert E. Mates and Paul Katz on versoHandwritten on verso: "1974" "32" circled Stamp on verso: "PHOTOGRAPHED BY ROBERT E. MATES AND PAUL KATZ"
- Georgia O'Keeffe, Ghost Ranch, NM, 1968; 2006.6.949; Newman, Arnold, 1918-2006; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 3/4 x 9 3/4 inches; Framed. Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe, Ghost Ranch New Mexico 1968Handwritten on verso: Georgia O'Keeffe, Ghost Ranch New Mexico 1968
  Portrait of O'Keeffe standing in profile, in the landscape, in front of an easel with a blank canvas with a rams skull with horns; O'Keeffe is wearing a blue jean jacket with her hair pulled back in a bun.
  Copyright Getty Images
- O'Keeffe sitting at Ghost Ranch, 1968; 2006.6.950; Newman, Arnold, 1918-2006; 1 Photographic Prints contact print 3 15/16 x 5 inches; Handwritten on recto: #5233-4Handwritten on recto: "#5233-4" "5233-4" Printed on verso: "KODAK PAPER"
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Living Room, 1981; 2006.6.951; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 8 x 10 inches; Signed on rectoSigned on recto; Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 4'
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Living Room, 1980; 2006.6.952; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 8 x 10 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 75'
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Patio, 1980; 2006.6.953; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Nichols 2b'
  Portrait of O'Keeffe sitting on a banco in the patio of her Abiquiu house surrounded by a collection of rocks; she is wearing a black suit coat, black pants, a white shirt and a black scarf which covers her hair; she sits with body turned slightly to viewer right, her left leg is crossed over her right knee and her arms are crossed over her lap, her face in partial profile, a shaft of diagonal light illuminates the midsection of her body and the collection of rocks around her feet in the foreground.
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Patio, 1980; 2006.6.954; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 3/4 x 4 3/16 inches; Handwritten on recto: "TAKe" Handwritten on verso: "NICHOLS 2a" Printed on verso: arrow pointing towards right "PEEL QUICKLY" arrow pointing towards left "POLAROID L04815008977B"
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Living Room, 1980; 2006.6.955; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 4 3/16 x 5 3/4 inches; Handwritten on recto: "TAKE." Handwritten on verso: "NICHOLS 7a" Printed on verso: arrow pointing towards right "PEEL QUICKLY" arrow pointing towards left "POLAROID L04815008977B"
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Abiquiu Studio with Sculpture by Juan Hamilton, 1980; 2006.6.956; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 3/4 x 4 3/16 inches; Handwritten on recto: "TAKE" Handwritten on verso: "NICHOLS 3" Printed on verso: arrow pointing towards right "PEEL QUICKLY" arrow pointing towards left "POLAROID L04815008977B"
- Georgia O'Keeffe and Mary Callery with Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe, 1945; 2006.6.957; Porter, Eliot Furness, 1909-1990; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 10 1/16 x 7 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on versoPrinted on recto: "EASTMAN SAFTEY-KODAK 33" Handwritten on verso: "PORTER 2" Label on verso: "AMON CARTER MUSEUM 3501 Camp Bowie Boulevard Post Office Box 2365 Fort Worth, Texas 76113-2365 Museum Number 810-45-9 Title Georgia O'Keeffe and Mary Callery, Ghost Ranch, New Mexico, September 1945 Artist Eliot Porter Size Medium Date Date of Negative This picture may be reproduced with written permission The Amon Carter Museum and must be accompanied by the credit line: Amon Carter Museum. Fort Worth. Stamp on verso: "NOTICE This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner of the work photographed. Amon Carter Museum Fort Worth, Texas" Printed on verso: "Agfa"""study purposes only
  Portrait of O'Keeffe sitting in a chair, in a wheelbarrow, modeling for mary Callery at a room at Ghost Ranch. Callery is standing and sculpting the head of O'Keeffe on a tripod sculpting stand. Callery wears a denim shirt and jeans and O'Keeffe is wearing a shawl and long skirt.; viga beams and adobe walls, ladders etc.
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Horse at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.959; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe with Horse at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.960; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.961; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.962; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.963; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.964; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.965; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.966; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.967; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe at Sapello Ranch, 1980; 2006.6.968; Pritzlaff, Richard G., 1902-1997; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 x 5 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe in Taos, New Mexico, 1929; 2006.6.969; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 15/16 x 8 1/8 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the title and what appear to be negative numbers along with a stamp from the Museum of New Mexico stating that this copy print is for study purposes only and reproduction requirements.
  Portrait of O'Keeffe sitting on a wooden bench dressed in a white shirt with a black sweater over her shoulders and a black skirt, ankles are crossed, hair pulled back with desert landscape in background.
- Georgia O'Keeffe with James Johnson Sweeney at American Academy, New York, 1963; 2006.6.970; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 10 x 8 inches; Stamp on verso: "WAINTROB-BUDD 145 WEST 71ST. ST. NEW YORK, NY 10023 (212)-874-1663" "123524" "WAINTROB-BUDD 145 WEST 71ST. ST. NEW YORK, NY 10023 (212)-874-1663" Handwritten on verso: "30-34"
- Georgia O'Keeffe with James Johnson Sweeney at American Academy, New York, 1963; 2006.6.971; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 10 x 8 inches; Handwritten on "34D" "34D" "AMER ACADEMY 5-22-1963" "41" circled Stamp on verso: "121000" "WAINTROB-BUDD 145 WEST 71ST. ST. NEW YORK, NY 10023 (212)-874-1663"
- Contact Prints of Georgia O'Keeffe, 1963; 2006.6.972; 1 Photographic Prints contact sheet 1st contact sheet 2 13/16 x 4 11/16 inches, 2nd contact sheet 5 13/16 x 1 5/8 inches; 1st contact print: Printed on recto: "KODAK PLUS X PAN FILM" "KODAK PLUS X PAN FILM" "KODAK S AFETY FILM" "30" "29" "36" "35" Handwritten on verso: "Roll #30 30-30 30-29 30-36 30-35" Stamp on verso: "WAINTROB-BUDD 145 WEST 71ST. ST. NEW YORK, NY 10023 (212)-874-1663" 2nd contact print: Printed on recto: "KODAK PLUS X PAN FILM" "KODAK PLUS X PAN FILM" "KODAK S AFETY FILM" cut off Printed on recto: "34" 32" "33" Handwritten on recto: "8 x 10" Handwritten on verso: "30" cut off "30-34 30-33 30-32" "WAINTROB-BUDD 145 WEST 71ST. ST. NEW YORK, NY 10023 (212)-874-1663"
  Contact prints of Georgia O'Keeffe and James Johnson Sweeney at the American Academy, New York.
- Unidentified Man, 1964; 2006.6.1059; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints color Polaroid print 2 7/8 x 3 3/4 inches; Handwritten on the back of the photograph is the flash exposure time.
  Portrait of a man with gray hair and with hand on his chin, blue eyes looking upward, dressed in a gray and white small checked shirt with white drapery as the backdrop.
- Unidentified Man, 1964; 2006.6.1060; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints color Polaroid print 2/7/8 x 3 3/4 inches
  Portrait of a man with gray hair a blue eyes, looking directly at the camera, dressed in a gray and white small checked shirt, white drapery as the backdrop.
- Unidentified Man, 1964; 2006.6.1061; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints color Polaroid print 2 7/8 x 3 3/4 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph is an inscription regarding the flash exposure.
  Portrait of a man with gray hair and with hand on his chin and cheek, blue eyes looking toward the camera, dressed in a gray and white small checked shirt with white drapery as the backdrop.
- Unidentified Woman, 1964; 2006.6.1062; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints color Polaroid print 2 7/8 x 3 3/4 inches
  Portrait of a young woman with short brown hair, wearing an orange and yellow checked shirt, sitting against a white upholstered cushion that is covered with an orange patterned bandana.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room, 1964; 2006.6.1063; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 2 7/8 x 3 3/4 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is an inscription regarding cloud filter control.
  Interior view of the Abiquiu house living room with furniture in shadow, white slipcovered chair near picture window, rocks on window ledge, view of large tree ( in snow?) through window. Processing roller marks across the emulsion as brown horizontal lines.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room, 1964; 2006.6.1064; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 2 7/8 x 3 3/4 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is an inscription referring to light control.
  Interior view of the Abiquiu house living room with white slipcovered furniture in semi-shadow, plants, ghost-like view of large tree through picture window. Processing roller marks across the emulsion as brown horizontal lines.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Living Room, 1964; 2006.6.1065; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 2 7/8 x 3 3/4 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is an inscription relating to cloud filter control.
- Skull, 1964; 2006.6.1066; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 2 7/8 x 3 3/4 inches
  Image of bleached cow skull with horns hanging on adobe wall, Processing roller marks across the emulsion as brown vertical lines.
- Insects on Leaf, 1964; 2006.6.1067; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 2 7/8 x 3 1/4 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is an inscription regarding light control dial.
  Closeup view of two insects facing each other on a leaf, reflections, dark rock in foreground, Processing roller marks across the emulsion as brown horizontal lines and marks.
- Insects on Leaf, 1964; 2006.6.1068; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 2 7/8 x 3 1/4 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is an inscription regarding the lighting dial.
- Jimson Weed, 1964; 2006.6.1069; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 3 3/4 x 2 7/8 inches
  Close up of a Jimson weed flower with dark leaves surrounding it, pistol and stamen visible, shaft of light hitting top of petal.
- Jimson Weed, 1964; 2006.6.1070; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 3 3/4 x 2 7/8 inches
  Close up portrait of the a white jimson weed flower; some of the petal edges are bent forward; partial shadow over pistol and stamen, flower surrounded by dark waxy leaves
- Jimson Weed, 1964; 2006.6.1071; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 3 3/4 x 2 7/8 inches